Risk Factor is a action film directed by Frank A. Caruso.
Alex Granger is a successful New York fashion photographer with a past - he
is a former CIA operative specializing in surveillance work.
Bored with his present life-style and craving adventure, Alex is lured back into the game by a
beautiful, mysterious woman, who just happens to be in partnership with a major arms dealer.
Alex is led to believe that he's being hired for industrial espionage and is paid a very large sum of money for his services.Former CIA partner is
hot on the trail of the arms dealers and when Alex is confronted with the truth, realizes he's being implicated in their schemes.
He is now caught between a "rock and a hard place" and must
do whatever needs to be done to save himself.
Alex Granger, played by Jalal Merhi.
Rick D'Angelo, played by Loren Avedon.
Eve, played by Elise Muller.
Damon Ramsay, played by Brett Halsey.
Hitman / photographer, played by Frank A. Caruso.
The Human Factor is a 1979 British neo noir film starring Nicol Williamson, Robert
Morley, and Richard Attenborough, and directed and produced by Otto Preminger.
The screenplay is by Tom Stoppard, based on the 1978
novel The Human Factor by Graham Greene.
It examines British espionage, and the difficulty of identifying
a mole in the ranks of an intelligence service.
This was Preminger's last film.